唇、あの人には 届かないし
With your lip movements you can’t reach anyone,
探しても無駄なんじゃないかな？
so isn’t it pointless even if you tried to?
君が息を吹き返したら
While you seem to breathe freely
逆に息を潜めた僕
I toned down my breathing.
知ってる
I knew that
君は死んでない
you’re not dead.
僕には 関係ないよ
It doesn’t matter to me.
なるべく
I don’t really
会いたくないな
want to see you.
たじろぐ姿は
Your wincing
好きの証
proofs you like me.
臆病なだけなのに
I’m not more than a coward
ロマンチスト気取り
and yet a romanticist; not a
じゃないと身が持たないし
feigned one and I don’t belong to myself.
でもまたすぐに
But again I’ll
後悔してる
regret it right after.
学習能力はゼロ
My ability to learn equals zero.
普段は
Usually I’m
ずる賢いよ
really devious.
君には通用しない
That doesn’t apply to you.
口から口に注ぎたい
I want to show you mouth-to-mouth,
ダメだろ
but I shouldn’t
無抵抗だし　今は
although you’re defenseless now…
こんな状況でも
You think this way about me
変な気持ちになる
but it starts to feel strange.
間違いなんて
Without a doubt
気にしない
I don’t care.
がむしゃらでした
It was reckless.
さよならはヤダ
I don’t want to bid farewell.
定めらぬうちに触れた
I can’t decide if you touched me within.